Guide to the Cornell Women's Club of Batavia records, 1934-2008.
Cornell Women's Club of Batavia records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Women's Club of Batavia records, 1934-2008.
41-6-3435
Cornell Women's Club of Batavia.
1.9 cubic foot.
Correspondence, Memorabilia, Newspapers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Victorian bird cage and copies of letters and clippings about it.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
In 1975, the club acquired a Victorian birdcage said to have been owned by Liberty Hyde Bailey. Over the years, the club annually auctioned off the cage; the winner enjoyed it for a year and then put it up for rebid. Proceeds went to the club's scholarship fund. Eventually the cage was given to Gertrude ("Red") H. Smith (Cornell Class of 1947), whose mother Mary Wright Harvey founded the club in 1934 and was its first president.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Victorian bird cage and copies of letters and clippings about it.
Includes meeting minutes, newspapers clippings, correspondence and a banner.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Women's Club of Batavia.; Bailey, L. H.(Liberty Hyde), 1858-1954.; Harvey, Mary Wright.; Smith, Gertrude Harvey.; Wright, Mary R.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University--Societies, etc.
Subjects:
Women--Societies and clubs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Guest Register for 40, 60, 65th Anniversaries (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Treasurer's Book, 1934-1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Notebook, 1934-1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Notebook, 1965-1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Notebook, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Notebook, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Notebook, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Notebook, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Notebook, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Notebook, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Notebook, 1985-1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Notebook, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Notebook, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Notebook, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Notebook, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Notebook, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Notebook, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Notebook, 2004-2007 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Notebook, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Banner (Box 3)